https://www.tocaloma.com/cookie-policy-us/

Hit enter to search or ESC to close
This page was last changed on October 21, 2020, last checked on October 21, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.tocaloma.com (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settingsYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Advertising cookiesWe do not use any advertising cookies on this website.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook and Instagram are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesWordFence
We use WordFence for website security.
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
wf-scan-issue-expanded-*
Functional
wfwaf-authcookie-*
12 hours
Determine if the user is logged in
Sharing
For more information, please read the WordFence Privacy Policy.Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Policy.Facebook
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
actppresence
1 year
Manage ad display frequency
Sharing
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Selling data to third partiesWe do not sell data to third parties11. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Tocaloma Summer Day Camp
PO Box 1460
Santa Monica, CA 90406
United States
Website: https://www.tocaloma.com
Email: campoffice@tocaloma.com
Phone number: 3103992267This cookie policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on April 10, 2020
Cookie Policy (US)
